and he had someone in here should put us over there you're the one who bought it for me your offspring who
right
i see
don't matter
mother married a smurf
nan
person
rune it
nan
holly i went to paris for six months that was the best time of my life version
except for this next phase of course
so any reason you worked in paris in particular is that where all the beautiful women in the world have to go through
well i speak a little a little french and i've always wanted to live there so after i graduated i went out there on a totally student budget i slept in a broom closet literally i started this firm in a supply closet literally the hangar
so we both know the value of closet space yeah
let me see some you work
nan
i know that i hit
you can sell it to us whenever we go to church
oh let me tell you about us had ruler we approach architecture a human level person
are you okay
i shriek
water
alien
feeling
nan
i doctor lee anthony venza
we got the results of your blood test back and it looks like the dyad the pam was the most likely cause fainting so what do as well
that would definitely explain what happened to you
nan
stop
tell her to start well tell him to stop what he's doing
when babbling about now she has explained to me why we're here yeah but being a very good friend and also good reason some need you to sit up and listen shallowest back
one night i was sitting
thinking about
how to leave each in
running whole thing in my mind
and he was staring at me
studying me
me saying a single word
he said that i could never leave him
that wherever i went
find me
that he would walk right up to me
wouldn't be able to see him
so that i'd know he was there
the night i left him i drugged him with that i lost the bottle at night
how it found it's way back to me
so what exactly are you saying lost a bottle found the button
nan
have a pile of ashes in a box that would disagree with you too silly
i don't know heist
nan
he has figured out a way to be invisible
he is a world leader in the field of optics i i i know that he could to this
something tells me you know exactly what i'm talking about
dead
see
nan
okay
that was his true genius knowing people's weaknesses
nan
he came up with the perfect way to torture you even in death
only thing more brilliant than inventing something that makes you invisible is not inventing
and you think it
you and i we got that in common
i was relieved
when i heard that he was dead
on sicily a size body
nan
a of win by bringing them back to life
hey
thanks so much for carving out the time to let me know how quote unquote suffocating i am to you what would you that i should have to say this but i never expected any of that money
i don't i don't know what you're talking about
email mean i sent me this morning
email that i feel about me don't ask me to bail you out of your personal life anymore if you're too stupid to know who the good guys aren't too weak to get away from that bad ones don't sob to me for charity i'm out i didn't send you the fucking email
he's he's twist
nan
adrian
agent sent me the email
am pleased
nan